Guide to the American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 37 Records WAG.265
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Legal Department Records, 1956-1986
  - New York City HHC: General Legal, 1977-1978; cuid5135 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - New York City HHC: General Legal, 1979-1984; cuid5136 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - New York Police Department: Improper Labor Practices, 1979-1980; cuid5137 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Parking Violations Bureau, 1979; cuid5138 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Pay Equity: AFSCME et al. v. State of Washington, Clippings, 1983-1984; cuid5139 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Pay Equity: AFSCME v. Washington, Comparable Worth Studies, 1974, 1976; cuid5140 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Pay Equity: AFSCME v. Washington, Petition for En Banc Hearing, 1985; cuid5141 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Pay Equity: AFSCME v. Washington, Pleadings, 1983-1985; cuid5142 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Pay Equity: AFSCME v. Washington, Press Releases, 1982-1985; cuid5143 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Pay Equity: AFSCME v. Washington, Settlement, 1985; cuid5144 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Pay Equity: AFSCME Publications, undated, 1980-1981; cuid5145 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Pay Equity: AFSCME Research Department Reports, 1982-1983; cuid5146 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Pay Equity: Chicago, AFSCME EEOC Filing, 1983; cuid5147 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Pay Equity: Comparable Worth Articles I, undated, 1980-1986; cuid5148 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Pay Equity: Comparable Worth Articles II, undated, 1980-1986; cuid5149 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Pay Equity: Comparable Worth Research Materials, 1980-1986; cuid5150 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Pay Equity: Gold, Michael Evans, "A Dialogue on Comparable Worth", 1984; cuid5151 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Pay Equity: Gross, Beverly, 1984-1985; cuid5152 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Pay Equity: Law Review Articles, 1982-1985; cuid5153 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Pay Equity: Los Angeles County Employees, SEIU Report, 1985; cuid5154 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Pay Equity: Minnesota Department of Employee Relations, Local Government Pay Equity Supplement for Cities, 1984; cuid5155 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Pay Equity: New York City, 1982-1985; cuid5156 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Pay Equity: New York City Office of the Mayor, Report on Status of Women in NYC Government, 1971; cuid5157 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Pay Equity: New York State Comparable Worth Study by Center for Women in Government, 1985; cuid5158 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Pay Equity: New York State Division of Human Rights, 1985; cuid5159 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Pay Equity: Newman, Winn Articles and Statements, undated, 1981-1985; cuid5160 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Pay Equity: Printed Material (Various Organizations), 1979-1985; cuid5161 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Pay Equity: U.S. Commission on Civil Rights Reports, 1984; cuid5162 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Pay Equity: U.S. Commission on Civil Rights, Winn Newman Testimony, 1984; cuid5163 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Pay Equity: U.S. General Accounting Office, Status of State Activities on Pay Equity, 1986; cuid5164 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Pay Equity: Women's Advocacy Committee of New York, Study on Women in NYC Government (Clerical Workers), 1972; cuid5165 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Santos, Rafael v. Security and Law Enforcement Employees, 1978-1978; cuid5166 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Santos, Rafael v. Security and Law Enforcement Employees: Background Materials, undated; cuid5167 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - School Breakfast Program, 1976-1977; cuid5168 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - School Breakfast Program: Community School Board Lists/Compliance, 1976; cuid5169 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - School Breakfast Program: Response to Demand Letter, 1976; cuid5170 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - School Breakfast Program: Legal Research, 1974-1976; cuid5171 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Tellez, Rogelio v. City of New York, 1975-1982; cuid5172 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Wage Controls, 1976; cuid5173 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor: Bargaining Rights, 1977; cuid5174 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Women in City Government United, et al. v. City of New York, et al.: Administrative, 1977-1983; cuid5175 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Background Materials, 1973, 1976-1977, 1980; cuid5176 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Background Materials, Legal, undated, 1971-1979; cuid5177 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Background Materials, Legislation, 1971, 1973; cuid5178 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Background Materials, Pension Plan, 1969-1970; cuid5179 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Background Materials, Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association (TIAA), 1975, 1981-1982; cuid5180 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Change of Attorney, 1977; cuid5181 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Class Action Status, 1975-1976; cuid5182 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Clippings, 1973-1980; cuid5183 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Correspondence I, 1973-1983; cuid5184 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Correspondence II, 1973-1983; cuid5185 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Internal Memoranda, 1973-1976; cuid5186 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Interrogatories I, 1975-1977, 1980; cuid5187 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Interrogatories II, 1975-1977, 1980; cuid5188 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Interrogatories III, 1975-1977, 1980; cuid5189 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Kinzel Commission Reports, 1976; cuid5190 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Memoranda I, 1975-1978, 1980-1982; cuid5191 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Memoranda II, 1975-1978, 1980-1982; cuid5192 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Memoranda III, 1975-1978, 1980-1982; cuid5193 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Motion for Summary Judgment, 1980; cuid5194 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Notes, 1976-1979; cuid5195 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Notice to Admit and Responses, 1976-1977, 1980; cuid5196 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Order to Show Cause, 1980; cuid5197 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Pleadings I, 1975-1982; cuid5198 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Pleadings II, 1975-1982; cuid5199 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Pleadings III, 1975-1982; cuid5200 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Program Planners Analysis, 1976; cuid5201 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Settlement Proposals I, 1977-1980; cuid5202 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Settlement Proposals II, 1977-1980; cuid5203 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Stipulations, 1975-1977, 1979-1980; cuid5204 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Transport Workers Union Case (Burns, Jackson, Miller, Summit, and Spitzer v. Lindner), MLC Amicus Curiae, undated; cuid5205 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Workers' Compensation, 1977-1984; cuid5206 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Youth Employment Act: Young Adult Conservation Corps, 1978; cuid5207 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Series IV: Communications Department Records, 1963-2004
  - Subseries IV:A: Edward Handman Records, 1972-1991.
    - City Budget: Clippings, 1978-1980; cuid5208 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Common Retirement Fund, 1981; cuid5209 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Contract Negotiations, 1980, 1987, 1990-1991; cuid5210 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Contract Negotiations: Clippings, 1977-1978; cuid5211 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Contract Negotiations: Clippings, 1979-1980; cuid5212 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Contract Negotiations: Clippings, 1987, 1990; cuid5213 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Contract Negotiations: Municipal Labor Committee Campaign, 1987; cuid5214 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: General, 1983-1989; cuid5215 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - DC 37 Film Strip, 1989; cuid5216 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - DC 37/AFL-CIO Conference: "Changing Situation of Workers and Their Unions", 1985; cuid5217 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - DC 37/AFL-CIO Conference: "Changing Situation of Workers and Their Unions": Correspondence, 1985-1986; cuid5218 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - DC 37/AFL-CIO Conference: "Changing Situation of Workers and Their Unions": Transcript, 1985; cuid5219 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1975): Chronology, 1974-1977; cuid5220 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1975): Clippings, undated; cuid5221 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1975): Clippings, 1973-1974; cuid5222 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1975): Clippings, Jan 1975-Jul 1975; cuid5223 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1975): Clippings, Aug 1975-Dec 1975; cuid5224 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1975): Clippings, 1976-1977; cuid5225 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1975): General, 1975-1976; cuid5226 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1975): Municipal Labor Committee Reports, ca.1976; cuid5227 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): Clippings, undated; cuid5228 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): Clippings, Oct 1990-Nov 1990; cuid5229 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): Clippings, Dec 1990-Jan 1991; cuid5230 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): Clippings, Feb 1991-Mar 1991; cuid5231 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): Clippings, Apr 1991; cuid5232 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): Clippings, May 1, 1991-May 15, 1991; cuid5233 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): Clippings, May 16, 1991-May 31, 1991; cuid5234 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): Clippings, Jun 1, 1991-Jun 20, 1991; cuid5235 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): Clippings, Jun 21, 1991-Jun 30, 1991; cuid5236 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): Clippings, Jul 1991-Aug 1991; cuid5237 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): General, 1990; cuid5238 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): General, Jan 1991-Mar 1991; cuid5239 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): General, Apr 1991-Jun 1991; cuid5240 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): Library Budget Cuts, cuid5241 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Handman, Edward: Biographical Information, undated; cuid5242 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Handman, Edward: Book Proposal, undated; cuid5243 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Handman, Edward: Journalism Syllabi, undated; cuid5244 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Handman, Edward: Op-Ed Articles, undated; cuid5245 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Handman, Edward: Op-Ed Articles, 1984-1990; cuid5246 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Handman, Edward: Testimony on State Government, 1987; cuid5247 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - It's Your City, It's Our Job Radio Show: Journalism Contests, 1988-1989; cuid5248 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - It's Your City, It's Our Job Radio Show Transcripts (Domestic Violence; Staten Island; Homeless), 1987-1989; cuid5249 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Labor Movement: Clippings, 1985-1986; cuid5250 (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Labor-Management Articles, undated, 1985, 1988; cuid5251 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - March on Washington for Jobs and Job Security, 1975; cuid5252 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - March on Washington for Jobs and Job Security: Clippings, 1975; cuid5253 (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Political Action: Mayoral Campaign (Dinkins), 1990; cuid5254 (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - Political Action: Presidential Campaign (Mondale-Ferraro), 1984; cuid5255 (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - Public Relations Campaign, undated, 1972, 1986-1988; cuid5256 (Box 40, Folder 32)
    - Reagan Budget: Clippings, 1984; cuid5257 (Box 40, Folder 33)
    - Reagan Budget: Impact on New York City, 1980-1984; cuid5258 (Box 40, Folder 34)
    - Williams, Franklin: Commentaries, 1983; cuid5259 (Box 40, Folder 35)
    - Window Guard Campaign, 1981; cuid5260 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Subseries IV:B: Bill Schleicher Records, 1992-2004.
    - AFSCME Convention (36th), 2004; cuid5261 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Bargaining: Notes, 2003; cuid5262 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Black History Month, 2004; cuid5263 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Blackout (Con Edison), 2003; cuid5264 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Building-Wide Meetings: Notes, 2003; cuid5265 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - City Budget, 2004; cuid5266 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - City Budget: Child Health Nurses, 2003-2004; cuid5267 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Clippings, 2002-2004; cuid5268 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Contract Negotiations, 2004; cuid5269 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Contract Negotiations: Fair Contract Rally, 2003; cuid5270 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: AFSCME, Insurance Fraud Claims, 2000; cuid5271 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Albert Diop and Martin Lubin Clippings, 1998, 2000; cuid5272 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Annual Return/Report of Employee Benefit Plan, 1992-1993; cuid5273 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Clippings and Articles, 1997-2000; cuid5274 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Correspondence, 1995-2000; cuid5275 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Financial Statements, 1996-1999; cuid5276 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Harold Hawson and Anthony Lawson v. DC 37 et al., 1999-2000; cuid5277 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Judicial Panel Decisions, 1999-2000; cuid5278 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: KPMG, "Report on Certain Financial Activities at AFSCME DC 37 and Funds" Book 1 of 3, I, 2001; cuid5279 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: KPMG, "Report on Certain Financial Activities at AFSCME DC 37 and Funds" Book 1 of 3, II, 2001; cuid5280 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: KPMG, "Report on Certain Financial Activities at AFSCME DC 37 and Funds" Book 2 of 3, 2001; cuid5281 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: KPMG, "Report on Certain Financial Activities at AFSCME DC 37 and Funds" Book 3 of 3, 2001; cuid5282 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: KPMG, "The Ratification Vote on the 1995 Economic Agreement: A Report to the General Council of AFSCME", 1999; cuid5283 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Labor Organization Annual Reports, 1989-1998; cuid5284 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Legal Transcripts, 2000; cuid5285 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Notes, 1999; cuid5286 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Press Releases, 1999-2001; cuid5287 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Printed Material, 1999-2000; cuid5288 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Reform Proposals, 2000; cuid5289 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Union Democracy Articles, 1998-1999; cuid5290 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence: General, 2001-2003; cuid5291 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Delegate Education, 2003; cuid5292 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - Delegates: Meeting Notes, 2001-2004; cuid5293 (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - Direct Election of Officers Dispute: Veronica Montgomery-Costa Testimony, 2004; cuid5294 (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - Editorials: Source Material, 2004; cuid5295 (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - Executive Board: Meeting Notes, 2001-2002; cuid5296 (Box 41, Folder 36)
    - Executive Board: Meeting Notes, 2003-2004; cuid5297 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Event Announcements: DC 37, 2003-2004; cuid5298 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Event Announcements: Other Organizations, 2003-2004; cuid5299 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Finances: Corruption Scandals, 2002-2003; cuid5300 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Financial Reports, 2003-2004; cuid5301 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Grassroots Lobby Institute: Meeting Notes, 2003; cuid5302 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Group Leaders: Meeting Notes, 2001-2004; cuid5303 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Group Leaders: Reports, Nov 2001-Feb 2002; cuid5304 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Group Leaders: Reports, May 2002-Feb 2003; cuid5305 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Group Leaders: Reports, Apr 2003-Sep 2004; cuid5306 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Health Care Benefits and Prescription Drug Coverage, 2003; cuid5307 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Immigrant Worker Freedom Ride, 2003; cuid5308 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - International Human Rights Day: AFL-CIO March, 2003; cuid5309 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Iraq War, 2004; cuid5310 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Labor Day, 2004; cuid5311 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education) Dispute: People of the State of New York v. Charles Hughes and Mildred Stephens, ca.1999; cuid5312 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education) Dispute: People of the State of New York v. Martin Hughes, Joseph Alfano, James Rose, and Richard Lewis, ca.1999; cuid5313 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Local 375 (CSTG) Dispute: CSTG v. DC 37, 1999; cuid5314 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Local 983 (Motor Vehicle Operators): Urban Park Rangers Retirement Program, 2003; cuid5315 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Local Presidents: Meeting Notes, 2001-2004; cuid5316 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Medicaid Budget Cuts, 2004; cuid5317 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Meeting Notes, 2003; cuid5318 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC), 2003; cuid5319 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - New York State AFL-CIO Constitutional Convention, 1996; cuid5320 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Officer Structure, 1999; cuid5321 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Per Diem Employees, 2002-2003; cuid5322 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Pinkett, Mary: Death of, 2003; cuid5323 (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - Political Action, 2003-2004; cuid5324 (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - Political Action: Presidential Campaign (Bush v. Kerry), 2004; cuid5325 (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - Press Releases, 2003-2004; cuid5326 (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - Rallies: Meeting Notes, 2003; cuid5327 (Box 42, Folder 31)
    - Reagan, Ronald: Death of, 2004; cuid5328 (Box 42, Folder 32)
    - Republican National Convention Protests, 2004; cuid5329 (Box 42, Folder 33)
    - Roberts, Lillian: Re-Election of, 2004; cuid5330 (Box 42, Folder 34)
    - Shop Stewards: Meeting Notes, 2003; cuid5331 (Box 42, Folder 35)
    - Staff: Meeting Notes, 2003; cuid5332 (Box 42, Folder 36)
    - Telephone Directory, 1997; cuid5333 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Subseries IV:C: Public Employee Press Research Files, 1963-1993.
    - Anti-Ballistic Missile System (ABM), 1969; cuid5334 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Blue Collar Locals: Citywide Strike, 1971; cuid5335 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Clippings: State Civil Service Eployees Association (CSEA) Strike, 1972; cuid5336 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: General, undated; 1963; 1970-1995; cuid5337 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Education Conference, 1963, 1985; cuid5338 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Event Programs and Announcements, undated, 1973-1978, 1992-1993; cuid5339 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Hospital Exposé, 1967-1968; cuid5340 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Hospital Exposé, 1971-1972; cuid5341 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Hospital Exposé: Bellevue Hospital, 1965-1971; cuid5342 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Hospital Exposé: Kings County Hospital, 1967-1972; cuid5343 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Hospital Exposé: Lincoln Hospital, 1966-1972; cuid5344 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Interview Notes: Members of Locals 372, 376, 384, 1113, 1407, 1501, 1502, 1549, 1597, and 2021, undated; cuid5345 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Leadership Conference, 1981; cuid5346 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education), 1973-1980; cuid5347 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education): Education Conferences, 1982, 1987, 1989; cuid5348 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Aides, UFT Challenge, 1973; cuid5349 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Hospital Strike, 1976; cuid5350 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Nurse's Aides Upgrading Program, 1966-1970; cuid5351 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Local 983 (Motor Vehicle Operators): Service Awards, 1975; cuid5352 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Local 1087 (Prevailing Rate Employees): Radio Repair Mechanics, 1978; cuid5353 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Local 1795 (Stationary Firemen): Safety Issues, 1970-1976, 1982, 1992; cuid5354 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC), 1967-1972; cuid5355 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - New York City HHC: Affiliation of Municipal and Voluntary Hospitals I, 1967-1968, 1972; cuid5356 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - New York City HHC: Affiliation of Municipal and Voluntary Hospitals II, 1967-1968, 1972; cuid5357 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - Notes, undated; cuid5358 (Box 43a, Folder 1)
    - Paycheck Cashing: Joseph Sperling v. Manufacturers Hanover Trust Company, 1976; cuid5359 (Box 43a, Folder 2)
    - Political Action: Goldberg-Paterson Campaign (Opposition to AFL-CIO Rockefeller Endorsement), 1970; cuid5360 (Box 43a, Folder 3)
    - Safety Committee Inspections, 1975-1976; cuid5361 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Substance Abuse Conference, 1984; cuid5362 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Taylor Law: Madison Square Garden Rally, 1967; cuid5363 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Taylor Law: Response to Sanitation and Teachers' Strikes, 1967-1968; cuid5364 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Series V: General Files, 1944-2000
  - Agreement: DC 37 and AFSCME, 1956; cuid5365 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Agreement: New York State Federation of Labor and New York State Industrial Union Council, 1958; cuid5366 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - AFL-CIO: Membership Education and Mobilization for Organizing Manual, undated; cuid5367 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - AFSCME: Affiliation Agreement with Lassen County Employees Association, undated; cuid5368 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - AFSCME: Employees' Pension Plan, undated; cuid5369 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - AFSCME: Financial Statements, 1996-1997; cuid5370 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - AFSCME: Secretary-Treasurer Educational Workshop, undated; cuid5371 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - AFSCME: Trust Agreement with National Bank of Washington, 1975; cuid5372 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - AFSCME, Community and Social Agency Employees Union (CSAE), Local 1707, 1958-1963; cuid5373 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - AFSCME, CSAE, Local 1707, 1964-1967; cuid5374 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - AFSCME, CSAE, Local 1707: Contested Election of Delegates to AFSCME Convention, 1964; cuid5375 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - AFSCME, Council 50, 1967-1969; cuid5376 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - AFSCME, Council 50: Mental Hospital Strike-- Clippings, 1968; cuid5377 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - AFSCME, Council 62, 1998; cuid5378 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - AFSCME Employees Federal Credit Union, 1972-1973; cuid5379 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - AFSCME International Convention (11th), 1958; cuid5380 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - AFSCME International Convention (11th): Correspondence, 1957-1958; cuid5381 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - AFSCME International Convention (11th) (Oversize), 1958; cuid5382 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - AFSCME International Convention (16th), 1966; cuid5383 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - AFSCME International Executive Board: Agendas, 1998; cuid5384 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - AFSCME International Executive Board: Minutes, 1968, 1975; cuid5385 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - AFSCME International Executive Board: Minutes, 1997-1998; cuid5386 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - AFSCME International Executive Board: Reports and Background Files, 1968; cuid5387 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - AFSCME International Executive Board: Reports and Background Files I, 1975; cuid5388 (Box 44, Folder 27)